Dunya Ramicova Costume Design Collection MSS.004
University of California, Merced Library
- Production Materials, Ephemera, and Process Notes, 66 Boxes
  - Box 100
    - The Electrification of the Soviet Union - Production Photographs (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - The Electrification of the Soviet Union - Publication: A Season at Glyndebourne (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Grownups - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director John Madden (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Grownups - Production Correspondence (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Grownups - Costume Plot and Scene Location (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Grownups - Costume Production Reference – American Repertory Theatre: Costume Lists (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Grownups - Playbill – American Repertory Theatre (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Grownups - Review – American Repertory Theatre (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Grownups - Production Cast List and Contact Sheet – The Lyceum Theatre, New York (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Grownups - Costume Production Reference – The Lyceum Theatre, New York: Costume Lists (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Grownups - Playbill - The Lyceum Theatre, New York (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Grownups - Reviews - The Lyceum Theatre, New York (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Grownups - Production Cast List and Contact Sheet – Mark Taper Forum, Los Angeles (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Grownups - Costume Production Reference – Mark Taper Forum, Los Angeles: Costume Lists (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Grownups - Playbill - Mark Taper Forum, Los Angeles (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Grownups - Reviews - Mark Taper Forum, Los Angeles (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Box 101
    - Bach Cantata 199 - Production Correspondence (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Bach Cantata 199 - Costume Production Reference (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Bach Cantata 199 - Reviews (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Bal - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Gregory Mosher (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Bal - Production Contact Sheet (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Bal - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Bal - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Bal - Playbill (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Andrei Serban (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Written Costume History Research (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Costume Production Reference: Planning Lists (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Costume Production Reference: Fabric Swatches (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Playbill (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Sganarelle (1977) - Reviews (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Production Cast List (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Description of Costumes and Their Production (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for Doctor in Spite of Himself (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for The Flying Doctor (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for The Imaginary Cuckold (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Sganarelle (1981) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for Forced Marriage (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Box 102
    - The Mikado - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - The Mikado - Production Cast Lists (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - The Mikado - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - The Mikado - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for all characters (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - The Mikado - Production Photograph (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - The Mikado - Playbill (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - The Mikado - Reviews (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Theodora - Written Research Notes (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Theodora - Written Exploration of Design Ideas (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Theodora - Production Faxes (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Theodora - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Character Descriptions, Research, Copies of Costume Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Theodora - Interview with Peter Sellars (1996) (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Theodora - Reviews: For 2003 Revival at Glyndebourne Festival Opera (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Theodora - Reviews: For Opera National du Rhin -2004 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Hang on to Me - Cast List (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Hang on to Me - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Hang on to Me - Letter from Julia Gillett, Production Manager, The Guthrie Theater (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Hang on to Me - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for all Characters (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Hang on to Me - Playbill and Opening Night Ticket (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Hang on to Me - Reviews (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Box 103
    - The Indian Queen - Notes from First Meeting with Peter Sellars (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - The Indian Queen - Written Preliminary Design Ideas (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - The Indian Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principals Costume Lists and Fabric Swatches (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - The Indian Queen - Costume Production Reference: Swatches of Fabric for Painted Head and Neck Kerchiefs (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - The Indian Queen - Costume Production Reference: Work Drawings (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - The Indian Queen - Costume Production Reference: Swatches of Fabric for Chorus Costumes (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - The Indian Queen - Costume Production Reference: Swatches of Fabric for Chorus Costumes (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - The Indian Queen - Libretto, Complete Libretto (revision #3) by Peter Sellars, May 27, 2013 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - The Indian Queen - The Golden Mask Award Nomination Letter (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - The Indian Queen - Score with Additional Music Inserted by Peter Sellars (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Box 104
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Costume Plot (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Samples of Color Elevations from George Tsypin's Scene Design (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Color Plot (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Visual Research (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Costume Production Reference: Costume Production Planning; Dressing Lists; Final Accounting of Money Spent on Production of Costumes (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Production Faxes (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Pre-production Publicity (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Playbill (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Reviews of De Nederlandse Opera 1993 Production (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Pelleas et Melisande - Reviews of Los Angeles Music Center Opera Production 1995 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Box 105
    - Griselda - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Griselda - Notes on Libretto (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Griselda - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Griselda - Costume Production Reference: Principles and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Griselda - Pre-Opening Publicity (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Griselda - Playbill (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Griselda - Reviews (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - The Flying Dutchman (1989) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Stephen Wadsworth (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - The Flying Dutchman (1989) - Costume Production Reference: Visual Research (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - The Flying Dutchman (1989) - Playbill (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - The Flying Dutchman (1989) - Reviews (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Stephen Wadsworth (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Production Information (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Artist Contact Sheet (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Production E-mails (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Costume Production Reference: Letter from DR to Stephen Wadsworth which accompanied rough drawings for Senta's new costume & Letter to Susan Denning which accompanied technical drawings for Flying Dutchman's new costume (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Costume Production Reference: Notes from meeting regarding hair and make-up (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Costume Production Reference: The Flying Dutchman First Entrances Costume Scene Breakdown (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Costume Production Reference: Rough drawings for Senta's new costumes, fabric swatches for her final designs, color copies of Dutch (Ghost) Crew designs worn in 2007 production which were re-made using new fabrics and swatches of these new fabrics (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - The Flying Dutchman (2007) - Playbill (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Box 106
    - Ghost Sonata - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Andrei Serban (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Ghost Sonata - Production Contact Sheet (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Ghost Sonata - Playbill (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Master Puntila and His Man Matti - Production Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Master Puntila and His Man Matti - Production Cast List (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Master Puntila and His Man Matti - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Keith Hack (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Production Cast List (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Dramaturgy Notes (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Yale School of Drama – Yale Repertory Theatre Design Department Assignments Chart Season 1978-1979 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Production Rehearsal Notes (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Costume Production Reference: Budget (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Geschichten aus dem Wiener Wald (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Tales from the Vienna Woods - Review (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - The Duchess of Malfi - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Chambers (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Production Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Production Cast List (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Scenery Sequences (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Scenery Images (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Costume Design Color Plot (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Costume Production Reference: Budget (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Pre-Production Publicity (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Playbill (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Search and Destroy (South Coast Repertory Theater) - Reviews (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Chambers (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Production Cast List (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Production Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Costume Production Reference: Budget (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Playbill (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Search and Destroy (Yale Repertory Theater) - Reviews (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Box 107
    - Le Grand Macabre - Written Research Notes (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Cast List (1997 Salzburger Festspiele production) (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Rehearsal Schedule (1997 Salzburger Festspiele production) (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancer, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Research, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancer, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Research, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Playbill (Salzburger Festspiele) (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Reviews (Salzburger Festspiele) (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Photographs (Salzburger Festspiele) (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Cast List (1998 Theatre du Chatelet, Paris) (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Rehearsal Schedule (1998 Theatre du Chatelet, Paris) (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Faxes (1998 Theatre du Chatelet, Paris) (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancer, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Costume Lists prepared for Theatre du Chatelet production (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Production Photographs (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Pre-production Publicity (Theatre du Chatelet) (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Playbill (Theatre du Chatelet) (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Le Grand Macabre - Reviews (Theatre du Chatelet) (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Box 108
    - Luisa Miller - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Francesca Zambello (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Luisa Miller - Notes on Libretto (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Luisa Miller - Photographs of Scene Design Model (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Luisa Miller - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Luisa Miller - Production Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Luisa Miller - Costume Production Reference: Costume Count (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Luisa Miller - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Research, Copies of Designs, Technical Drawings, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Luisa Miller - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Research, Copies of Designs, Technical Drawings, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Luisa Miller - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Research, Copies of Designs, Technical Drawings, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Luisa Miller - Costume Production Reference: Costume Narrative (how costumes are worn in each scene) (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Luisa Miller - Pre-Opening Publicity (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Luisa Miller - Reviews (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Box 109
    - An American Tragedy - An American Tragedy (a Brief Synopsis) (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - An American Tragedy - Written Research Notes (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - An American Tragedy - Notes on Principal Characters and Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - An American Tragedy - Letter from Dunya Ramicova to Francesca Zambello, Letter A (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy - Letter from Dunya Ramicova to Francesca Zambello, Letter B (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - An American Tragedy - Letters to Joe Clark, Metropolitan Opera (Met) Technical Assistant Manager, Borhan Ahmed, Met Resident Assistant to Costume Designer, and Jeannique Prospere, An American Tragedy Associate Costume Designer (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - An American Tragedy - Production E-mails (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - An American Tragedy - Scenic Color Reference Charts and Note from Adrianne Lobel (January 6, 2004) (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - An American Tragedy - Pictorial Research (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - An American Tragedy - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancers, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, and Costume Lists (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - An American Tragedy - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancers, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Technical Drawings (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - An American Tragedy - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Dancers, Chorus, and Supernumeraries: Technical Drawings (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Box 110
    - An American Tragedy - Fabric Color Plot and Fabric Shopping Guide (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - An American Tragedy - Fabric Color Plot and Fabric Shopping Guide (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - An American Tragedy - Fabric Swatches (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - An American Tragedy - Fabric Swatches (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy - Fabric Swatches (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - An American Tragedy - Costume Production Planning Chart and To Do List (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - An American Tragedy - Design and Style Breakdown Chart for Costumes Worn by Chorus Women (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Box 111
    - An American Tragedy - Lists of Headgear (buy and/or build), Gloves, and Cravats (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - An American Tragedy - Metropolitan Opera Costume Shop Cutter (Draper) Assignment Chart (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - An American Tragedy - Chorus Fitting Notes for Seamless Costumes (September 27, 2005) (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - An American Tragedy - Costume Budget (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy - Scene Breakdown (Costume Plot) (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - An American Tragedy - Metropolitan Opera Production Schedule for An American Tragedy (July8, 2003) (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - An American Tragedy - Production Cast List (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - An American Tragedy - Metropolitan Opera 2005-2006 Season Schedule (as of December 9, 2004) (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - An American Tragedy - An American Tragedy Principal Singers' Photographs (Head Shots and Met Production Shots) (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - An American Tragedy - Pre-opening Publicity (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - An American Tragedy - Playbill (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - An American Tragedy - Reviews (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - An American Tragedy - Piano / Vocal Score (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Box 112
    - Doctor Atomic - Libretto by Peter Sellars (Act I as of October 8, 2004) (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Doctor Atomic - E-mail (incomplete) from Los Alamos Historical Society (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Doctor Atomic - Letters from Former Los Alamos Manhattan Project Scientists (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Doctor Atomic - San Francisco Opera Pre-production Publicity (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Doctor Atomic - San Francisco Opera Performance Reviews (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Doctor Atomic - San Francisco Opera 2005 Production Ancillary Events (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Doctor Atomic - Pre-Production Publicity for Der Nederlandse Opera Performance June, 2007 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Doctor Atomic - Der Nederlandse Opera Performance June, 2007 Reviews (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Doctor Atomic - Wonder Are many, the Making of Doctor Atomic Documentary Reviews (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Doctor Atomic - E-mail from Jon Else, Director of Wonders Are Many, the Making of Doctor Atomic (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Doctor Atomic - Pre-Production Publicity for The Lyric Opera of Chicago Performance December, 2007 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Doctor Atomic - The Lyric Opera of Chicago Performance Reviews (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Box 113
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Francesca Zambello (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Production Information: Glimmerglass Opera (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Production Correspondence (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Preliminary Costume Plot and Scene Breakdown (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Preliminary Costume Count and Breakdown (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Visual Research (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Costume Production Reference: Technical Drawings (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Fabric Swatches (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Fabric Swatches (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Fabric Swatches (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - New York City Opera 1977 Production Schedule (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - New York City Opera Contact Sheet and List of Chorus (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Costume Production Reference: Description of Costumes (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Iphigenie en Tauride - Photographs of Scene Model (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Box 114
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Production Contact Sheet (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Notes Regarding Rehearsal Schedule (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Synopsis of the Opera (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Production Costume Reference: Costume Plots (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Production Costume Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for all Characters (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Welcome Speech by Peter Sellars for PepsiCo Summerfare Performances (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Giulio Cesare in Egitto - Playbill (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Tannhauser - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Tannhauser - Costume Production Reference: Lists: Counts of all Costume Pieces for Chorus and Principals (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Tannhauser - Costume Production Reference: Principals and Chorus: Copies of Designs (Chorus Only), Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Tannhauser - Costume Production Reference: Principals and Chorus: Copies of Designs (Chorus Only), Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Tannhauser - Visual Research (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Tannhauser - Lyric Opera of Chicago 1988-1989 Subscription Service Brochure (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Tannhauser - Reviews (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Synopsis (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Written Research (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Continuity Breakdown (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Location Breakdown (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Shooting Schedule (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Cast List with Contact Information (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for All Characters (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - The Cabinet of Dr. Ramirez - Production Photographs (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Box 115
    - Mathis der Maler - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Peter Sellars (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Mathis der Maler - Preliminary Costume Plot Notes (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Mathis der Maler - Production Cast List (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Mathis der Maler - Production Faxes (Box 115, Folder 4)